fantasyleague.com 2001-12-01

# Fantasy League

**This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for http://www.fantasyleague.com**

Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices. We agree to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site
  2. The organization collecting the information 
  3. How the information is used 
  4. With whom the information may be shared 
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Fantasy League Limited's control 
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you feel that we are not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact Tom Lehane at the Fantasy League offices by sending an email to privacy@fantasyleague.com or writing to Fantasy League Limited, 5-12 Mandela Street, London NW1 0DU, England. 

**Information Collection and Use**

If you have come to this site directly from an advertising banner, search engine or by entering the URL in your browser Fantasy League is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Fantasy League collects information from our users at several different points on our website. Should you enter this site having come from an Affiliate Site (one promoting our game with their own content) then the data you enter may be shared with that affiliate but only if they have clearly indicated this on the referring page that you have come from. 

**Registration**

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**Order**

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Contests or monthly Draws that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. 

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Fantasy League Limited are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as post code, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Tell-A-Friend (Challenge a Mate)**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Fantasy League Limited will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Fantasy League Limited stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Fantasy League at remove@fantasyleague.com to request the removal of this information from their database. 

**Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. 

**Special Offers**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

**Site and Service Updates**

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by emailing us at remove@fantasyleague.com 

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

|  |
